const quizData = {
  quizzes: [
    // 저축 카테고리
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "첫번째 문제",
      choices: ["않되나요", "안되나요", "안대나요"],
      correct: "안되나요"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "두번째 문제",
      choices: ["몇일", "몉일", "며칠"],
      correct: "며칠"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "세번째 문제",
      choices: ["설거지", "설겆이", "설겉이"],
      correct: "설거지"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "네번째 문제",
      choices: ["나중에 뵈요", "나중에 봬요", "나중에 봬어요"],
      correct: "나중에 봬요"
    },
    { 
      id: 5,
      question: "다섯번째 문제",
      choices: ["돼다", "되요", "되어요"],
      correct: "되어요"
    },
    { 
      id: 6,
      question: "여섯번째 문제",
      choices: ["왼만하면", "웬만하면", "왠만하면"],
      correct: "웬만하면"
    },
    { 
      id: 7,
      question: "일곱번째 문제",
      choices: ["금세", "금새", "금셰"],
      correct: "금세"
    },
    { 
      id: 8,
      question: "여덟번째 문제",
      choices: ["할께요", "할게요", "할꼐요"],
      correct: "할게요"
    },
    { 
      id: 9,
      question: "아홉번째 문제",
      choices: ["어따 대고", "얻다 데고", "얻다 대고"],
      correct: "얻다 대고"
    },
    { 
      id: 10,
      question: "열번째 문제",
      choices: ["데물림", "대물림", "되물림"],
      correct: "대물림"
    }
  ]
}
export default quizData;